sokrati.com 2010-11-28

# Sokrati: Pay for Performance Search Engine Marketing (SEM) Solution

---  
|  |  |   |  |  |  |   
---|---|---|---|---|---|---  
|  | 

|   
---  
  
| Sokrati LLC ( **"Sokrati"** ) provides technology and services that enable industry-leading companies ( **"Sokrati Client** (s) **"** ) to use online search engines to acquire customers ( **"Buyers"** ) and maximize returns on marketing spend. 

This Privacy Policy describes the Sokrati practices for gathering, storing, using and disseminating information. By visiting this website you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with the terms and conditions set forth below, please do not use or access the Sokrati services. By accepting this Privacy Policy, you expressly consent to the use and disclosure of your personally identifiable information as outlined below. This policy may be changed from time to time. All changes will be posted to this site and you are encouraged to periodically check back to this site for any changes to the privacy policy.  
  
---  
A. INFORMATION COLLECTION  
If you are using the Search Marketing services of Sokrati (the "Services"), whether through Sokrati or Agencies powered by Sokrati, Sokrati may collect demographic and geographic information of the visitors that are referred to your site. Sokrati may also collect behavioral patterns of these visitors like but not limited to : (1) Purchase information (2) Registration information (3) other pages browsed on your web site (4) respond to special offers, contests or surveys. This information is solely used for optimization purposes of your search engine campaigns.   
   
B. COOKIES  
"Cookies" are data files that may be downloaded to your computer when you visit the Sokrati site or a Sokrati Client site powered by Sokrati and permit the Sokrati server to identify your browser whenever you interact with the Sokrati site or a Sokrati Client site powered by Sokrati. Sokrati uses cookies to recognize repeat visits by users of its site and to collect information about its users' interactions with the Services. These cookies contain identification information that enables us to streamline your experiences using the Services. You may set your browser software to reject cookies, but you will be required to reenter your login information each time you access the Services, and you may not be able to optimize the features of the Services. In some cases, you will not be able to access Services if cookies are disabled.   
   
D. REVIEW AND MODIFICATIONS TO YOUR PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION.  
   
**If you are a Sokrati Client,** you may add, modify or update your personal information by accessing your account settings from the Sokrati home page when you log in to the Services. Through your Personal Account Settings, you may also determine how and when that personal information is distributed.   
   
E. LINKS TO OTHER SITES  
As a part of the Services, Sokrati provides links to web sites operated by third parties. Sokrati is not responsible for the information collection or privacy practices or the content of those third party sites.  
   
F. SECURITY  
Sokrati stores personally identifiable information obtained through registration securely and considers it part of the assets of its business. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, Sokrati has put in place physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information it collects online. However, data security is a constantly evolving art and science. You should consider any communication that you transmit to Sokrati (such as data, questions or answers, comments, or suggestions) as non-confidential, and agree that Sokrati will not be liable or responsible if information that belongs to you is intercepted and used by an unintended recipient.  
   
H. FURTHER INFORMATION  
If you have any questions about anything in this Privacy Policy, or about collection of personally identifiable information, or information generally, please contact Sokrati as follows:  
   
Sokrati LLC  
812 5th Ave E  
Seattle, WA 98109  
   
You may also use the above contact information if you think any information about you is inaccurate, incomplete, or if you want to change the sort of information about you that Sokrati may have collected.  

|  |
